I want first to attend to the viewers all over the world,
because they are more in number, than we that are here.
Viewers, wherever you are and whatever condition you are in -
I want to assure you that we are there and you are here.
Distance is not a barrier.
You are with us because you believe that it is the will of God to heal you.
You believe that it is His will to set you free from every infirmity.
That is why you are with us.
Whatever medium you are using to view us,
whatever medium you are using to watch us right now, viewers,
whatever situation you are in,
give thanks to God for sending His Word to set you free today.
I say, "You are free, in the name of Jesus!"
We decree that words: you are free in the name of Jesus!
Right now, God sent forth His Word and healed us.
You are healed, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Come on!
Viewers all over the world,
the same anointing that is working here
has been transferred to whatever place you are in.
Receive that anointing, in the name of Jesus!
Anointing that heals, that blesses, that saves, and that sets free - every infirmity.
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever situation you are in, are you sick?
What is the condition?
In your blood, fluid, tendons, kidneys,
be free, in the name of Jesus !
As you are watching this lady being set free from the demon that possesses her -
viewers, be free, in the name of Jesus!
Be free!
I say - you demon, loose your grip!
You infirmity, loose your grip!
Loose your grip!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Viewers, as this woman is being set free from that disease
that has put her in bondage for many years,
viewers, whatever bondage you are in, be free, in the name of Jesus!
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Come on!
Who are you?
Viewers, you are watching this sister being set free from whatever affliction.
I say, you are free, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever you are - are you in the hospital?
In prison yard?
Where can you go from His presence?
Come on!
Hey!
Viewers, look here.
Wherever you are, all over the world - what is your condition?
Whatever challenges you are in -
I say, you infirmity, loose your grip!
Loose your grip!
That sickness in your bone, in your fluid, in your tendon, in your kidney -
right now I command it out, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I restore you right now, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Viewers all over the world, whatever medium you are using to watch us, to view us right now,
I say to you that distance is not a barrier.
Receive your healing!
You can see people getting healed and getting delivered.
Right now, I say - receive your healing, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Never a sickness that Jesus cannot heal.
In the name of Jesus!
I am touching you, viewers!
Come out!
Look here!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Viewers, watch what is going on.
She is a contact point.
Come out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Get healed, viewers!
Get healed of your sickness!
Your affliction is over!
Your disease is over!
Come here. You go! Go this way.
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Whatever medium you are using to view us, I say that you are declared free!
As you see people being declared free, you are declared free!
As you see people being set free, you are set free!
As you see people being healed, you are healed!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Come on!
Look here!
Viewers all over the world, as you can see her being set free, you are set free, in the name of Jesus!
As you can see her being set free, you are set free, in the name of Jesus!
As you can see her being healed, you are healed, in the name of Jesus!
As you can see her being blessed, you are blessed, in the name of Jesus!
Receive your freedom!
Receive your freedom, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, are you in this situation or your situation is greater than this?
Remember, never a sickness Jesus cannot cure
and never a disease Jesus cannot heal.
Stand up!
Look here!
Viewers, get healed, in the name of Jesus!
You are free!
Thank you, Jesus, I am healed!
Thank you, Jesus, I can walk!
Viewers all over the world, what is our situation?
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Stop it!
Viewers all over the world, whatever bondage you are in, be it affliction,
hardship, infirmity - I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Just as this woman has been released, you are released, in the name of Jesus!
Just as this woman is being released, you are released, in the name of Jesus!
Come out!
Viewers, she is being delivered from a demon.
Right now, it is time to set her free!
Be free right now, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Take her out!
T.B. Joshua!
Viewers, you can see her calling me by name.
I don't mind whatever name she calls me.
I want to restore her salvation, her soul is dear to me.
Right now, viewers, call me whatever name you want to call me.
Hallelujah!
What is your situation, viewers?
Be set free, in the name of Jesus!
Thank you, Lord!
Man of God, deliver me!
I have a chronic headache, I cannot sleep for 3 months now.
Even if I take tablet, I cannot sleep.
Viewers, what is your own bondage?
What's your own predicament?
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
This woman will be released and you too will be released, in the name of Jesus!
This woman will be set free and you will be set free, in the name of Jesus!
This woman will be delivered and you will be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Stand Up!
Come on!
Viewers, watch you have been set free!
She is free.
Thank you, Jesus!
Come on!
Viewers, this woman is being set free!
Whatever challenges she has, Jesus knows.
Get ready to be set free!
Distance is not a barrier.
Are you connected?
You are set free, in the name of Jesus!
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Can you see him under the influence of familiar spirit?
Whatever your challenges are, you are declared free, in the name of Jesus!
As this man is being declared free, as this man is being exposed, the grip of satan has been broken today.
Be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Come out!
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God, as you send your testimony.
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Viewers, see the manifestation of evil spirits.
Whatever familiar spirits you are under -
are you under bondage of familiar spirits,
spirits of killing, stealing and destruction,
spirits of poverty, hardship?
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Be set free!
Be set free, in the name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Viewers, you are set free!
As this woman is being set free from familiar spirit, be set free!
As this woman is being set free from evil spirit, be set free!
Be set free!
Viewers all over the world, be set free!
Viewers all over the world, be set free, in Jesus' mighty name!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Man of God, have mercy on me!
I have fracture of the lumbar spine, I have diabetes.
I have fracture of the lumbar spine for 5 years; I cannot walk, squat or raise my hands.
Man of God, have mercy on me!
Viewers, whatever medium you are using to view us,
listen - never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Look at the situation here.
Look at the situation at hand.
Do you have a similar case, greater or deadly one?
Whatever name, whatever situation - never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Whatever familiar spirit -
are you under bondage of certain spirits -
your forefathers', ancestrals'?
Just name them.
I say to you - Jesus is here to capture you.
Be captured!
Be delivered!
Be delivered.
Be captured!
Be delivered!
Be captured for the glory, in Jesus' name!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Thank you, Jesus, I'm healed!
Man of God, help me!
I have difficulty in walking.
I had an accident and I have an ankle trauma.
Please, man of God, help me!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
I had an accident, I cannot walk, I cannot do anything.
Here you have this French speaking country.
And this is the situation she has been in for how many years?
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
3 months ago she had an accident and she could not do anything since that time.
She is from a French speaking country?
Whether it is Togo or Lome, it is French speaking.
With God all things are possible.
No matter the situation you are in.
After your healing, you have to reduce your stature.
It's a burden - this body.
So to reduce this stature is not to eat anything -
not everything you see!
You have to reduce this stature!
You will be healed and I will make sure that you reduce this stature.
So people in French speaking countries - never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Never a disease Jesus cannot cure.
Right now, be rescued!
Be healed!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Thank you, Lord, in Jesus Christ's name.
Come out!
Stand up!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
I say, you should reduce your stature!
Reduce your stature!
Stand up!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Man of God, please, help me!
I have difficulty in walking.
I have sickle cell anaemia.
Man of God, please help me - I have difficulty in walking.
For how many years?
For the past 3 years, man of God.
Can you talk to the world?
You have been in this condition for the past 3 years.
How has life been?
Life has been difficult; school has been very slow because I cannot go to school effectively.
I cannot do anything at home.
OK, it's alright.
Listen to that!
The young ones all over the world, new generation, listen to what the little one is saying.
She is here because she believes that Jesus is the Healer.
She believes that it is the will of God to heal her.
So this is an education for you, young ones out there, to accept Jesus and follow God.
Never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Never a problem Jesus cannot solve.
All these problems that you are talking about all over the world - Jesus can surmount them.
So now, after your healing, follow Jesus.
How many years have you been in this bondage?
For the past 3 years.
Thank you, Lord!
Come on!
Take it from her!
What is the cause of this problem?
Sickle cell anemia.
Oh, my God!
It's in your blood.
Thank you, Jesus!
I command that sickness in your blood, in your fluid, in your tendons - right now,
loose your grip, in the name of Jesus!
Come out!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Thank you, Jesus, I'm healed!
Thank You, Jesus!
I can walk now!
Man of God, please, help me!
I've been under the bondage of sleep apnoea for the past 5 years.
I cannot sleep without this machine.
For the past 5 years I sleep with it, and I carry this machine anywhere I'm going to.
This is how I use the machine.
Whenever I want to sleep, I put the face mask on and then I put on the machine.
Without the machine it can result to heart attack.
I've been to Thailand, Spain seeking medical attention.
Man of God, please, help me!
I equally have heart disease...
Viewers all over the world, he believes that he will be healed;
that is why he is here.
He believes that it is the will of God to heal him and set him free.
That is why he is here.
Yes!
The Lord is ready to send his Word and heal him.
Are you ready, viewers?
Whatever situation you are in, are you ready to receive your healing?
Whatever situation you are in, do you believe, it is God's will to heal you,
to deliver you and set you free?
Right now, get ready.
He will be delivered and you will be delivered.
Get ready!
As he is being delivered, you will be delivered.
As he is being healed, you will be healed!
As he is being set free, you will be set free,
In the name of Jesus!
Hallelujah!
Come on!
Viewers, get ready to receive your healing!
Receive your healing!
Receive your deliverance!
As this man is being healed, being delivered - be delivered!
Right now!
This man is being delivered!
This man is free!
Be free!
This man is healed - be healed!
Be delivered!
In the name of Jesus!
Thank you, Jesus, I'm free!
I will no longer need this machine.
I'm healed, in Jesus' name!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Man of God, I have difficulty in walking due to the fracture of the tibia in my right leg.
I cannot walk. Help me, man of God!
Hear him saying: "Help me, Lord!"
Viewers all over the world, say: "Help me, Lord!"
Heal me, I shall be healed.
Save me, I shall be saved.
Deliver me, I shall be delivered!
Bless me and I will be blessed!
Hallelujah!
Hallelujah, thank you!
Watch your screen!
Watch your screen, viewers!
Come out!
Viewers, receive!
Receive!
The SCOAN Sunday Prayer Line
Stand up!
Thank you, Jesus!
Give thanks to God for your freedom!
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God, as you send your testimony.
Engage with God!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work
in our generation today and stay up to date with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 08/07/2018
CR Robert Begier 10/04/2019